[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I already arranged everything.
Security will be on their way
too
so don't worry anymore.
[PING] I'll make
sure you're safe.
What are you doing here?!
- [SLAP LANDS]
- [ZIA GRUNTS]
You should be asking her
why she's here in the mansion!
You're really shameless,
aren't you?
- [SLAP LANDS]
- [ZIA GRUNTS]
What if I dropped a flower pot
on you instead, huh?
You two-faced fraud!
You're the fraud!
Scammer!
[PING] What are you talking
about?
Presenting her Uncle Dennis!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Uncle Dennis,
what are you doing here?
Now's not really the time
for you to be borrowing money...
I came here to tell the truth.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You're adopted, June!
That's not true!
How much did you pay him?
Just because we didn't lend you
money,
you're already turning
to this fraud of a lawyer!
[PING] And all of the records
and credible witnesses
point that June
is indeed a Rose.
You're still defending
this scammer?!
This peasant is just pretending
as a Rose
to get Don Nato's money!
[DENNIS] She is her mother's
daughter
but she is not
her father's!
That's why she is not a Rose!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ima?
Is is true?
Am I adopted?
Ima!
[THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]